Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. New York Office. Media Center Audiovisual Collection, 1953-2015 and undated RL.00734
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Video, 1955-2008; undated; 5
  - Detroit--Compilation reel, 1996 (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-055)
  - Detroit--Eyes on Thompson: Steve Davis, Mike Kalasunas, Malachy Walsh, 1993 (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-056)
  - Detroit--Firestone Recall "Ford Safety First" Jacques Nasser, Undated (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-057)
  - Detroit--Ford 50th Anniversary, 1993 (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-058)
  - Detroit--Ford/JWT 50th Anniversary Observance, 1993 (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-059)
  - Detroit--Ford Division Ad Age Research Phase III, 1994 (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-060)
  - Detroit--Ford Division Ad Age Research Phase III, 1994 (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-061)
  - Detroit--International Ford 25th anniversary: Italy "Man in Chair"; Netherlands "High Involvement", Undated (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-062)
  - Detroit--MS Society of Portugal "Baby" 1:29, 1995 (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-063)
  - Detroit--MS Society of South Africa "Drunk" :55, 1997 (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-064)
  - Detroit--New Life in the City: The Greening of Detroit 12:00, Undated (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-065)
  - Detroit--Old Commercials 7:00, Undated (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-066)
  - Detroit--Orientation Week part I, 1994 (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-067)
  - Detroit--Presbyterian Villages of Michigan: Downtown Detroit Aerials, Undated (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-068)
  - Detroit--Probe "Honey Performs"; Windstar "Word Change", 1994 (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-069)
  - Detroit--Professional Development Program: Bruce Rooke "Ford Truck Creative", 1994 (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-070)
  - Detroit--Professional Development Program: Peter Stroh "Marketing Services at JWT", 1993 (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-071)
  - Detroit--Professional Development Program Session 1: How the Carhartt Account Was Won, Undated (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-072)
  - Detroit--Professional Development Program Session 4: Roy Field "Financial Management of an Account", Undated (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-073)
  - Detroit--Professional Development Program Session 5: Ford International Advertising, Undated (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-074)
  - Detroit--Professional Development Program Session 11: Norm Ponkey "The JWT Yellow Pages Story", Undated (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-075)
  - Detroit--Professional Development Program Session 12: Kevin Dolan "Snapshot of JWT International", Undated (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-076)
  - Detroit--Professional Development Program Session 13: Roland Sharette "Case Historical--Ford", Undated (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-077)
  - Detroit--Professional Development Program Session 13: Roland Sharette "Case Historical--Ford", Undated (Box V2, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-078)
  - Detroit--Spoof reel 16 spots, 1993 (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-079)
  - Detroit--The More Creative the Ad, the Harder It Works, Undated (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-080)
  - Dick Van Dyke Show "All About Laura", 1994 (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-081)
  - Drug Enforcement Administration--It Never Went Away: Voices of Heroin in the 90s" 11:56, Undated (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-082)
  - Financial Analysts Creative Reel, 1996 (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-083)
  - Finding Solutions: Campaign Development Stages 24:00, Undated (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-084)
  - Finding Solutions: Campaign Development Stages 24:00, Undated (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-085)
  - The Ford Car Creative Product (Mike Priebe", 1994 (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-086)
  - Ford Division--6 spots, 1995 (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-087)
  - Ford Division--Ford Historical Ad Age Research Phase II, 1994 (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-088)
  - Ford Division--Historical spots for Ad Age Research, 1994 (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-089)
  - Ford International Advertising (Gary Belgrave), 1994 (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-090)
  - Galileo Research--Menopausal Study Group 2 Seeking Suffers, 2006 (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-091)
  - Galileo Research--Menopausal Study Group 1 Seeking Suffers, 2006 (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-092)
  - Galileo Research--Menopausal Study Group 3 Work Full Time, 2006 (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-093)
  - Galileo Research--Menopausal Study Group 4 Doctors OB/GYN, 2006 (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-094)
  - Galileo Research--Menopausal Study Thursday, 2006 (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-095)
  - Galileo Research--Menopausal Study Friday, 2006 (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-096)
  - General History of Print/History of Broadcast, Undated (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-097)
  - General History of Print/History of Broadcast Traveling exhibit modules, 1993 (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-098)
  - Goodyear--"Generations" 10:30, 1998 (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-099)
  - Goodyear--"Serious Freedom", 1997 (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-100)
  - Hate (film) (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-101)
  - JWT Close-Up ads compilation, 1997 (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-102)
  - JWT Management transition/Don Johnston Biltmore, 1974 (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-103)
  - JWT USA, 1995 (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-104)
  - JWT USA, 1996 (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-105)
  - JWT/West traveling archives video 14:00, 1994 (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-106)
  - JWTwo--Behind Closed Doors with Joan Lunden: Madison Ave./Domino's and JWT segment, 2003 (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-107)
  - JWTwo--Behind Closed Doors with Joan Lunden: Madison Ave./Domino's and JWT segment, 2003 (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-108)
  - JWTwo--Suzanne Powers, 2005 (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-109)
  - Kellogg's Nutrigrain Ironman campaign, Undated (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-110)
  - Kodak "Scratch and Win" Singlish, British English and American English versions, 1995 (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-111)
  - Kraft Shake and Bake Potatoes "Heritage" :30, 1995 (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-112)
  - Leadership Through Innovation, Undated (Box V3, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-113)
  - London--Agency film, Undated (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-114)
  - London--Autumn showreel, Undated (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-115)
  - London--Kit Kat, Persil, Entemann's commercials, 1996 (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-116)
  - London--Oxo history reel, 1996 (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-117)
  - London--Summer showreel, 2000 (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-118)
  - Manila--Q1 submission, 2000 (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-119)
  - Media Center transfer reel, 2002 (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-120)
  - Mumbai (Hindustan Thompson)--Bungle Book by Walt Dismayed; South and East Asia Managers Conference, 1989 (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-121)
  - National MS Society PSA campaign, 1996 (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-122)
  - Nepal--Fair and Lovely "I Want the Best" campaign with subtitles, Undated (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-123)
  - Nepal--OK Soap; Wheel Powerons; Himal Magazine, Undated (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-124)
  - North America reel, 1992 (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-125)
  - North America reel, 1992 (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-126)
  - North America reel, 1992 (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-127)
  - Oscar Mayer Wieners "Marching Song", 1963 (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-128)
  - Press coverage of Ford sponsorship of Schindler's List, Undated (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-129)
  - Professional Development Program--Brad Phillips "From Storyboard to Commercials", Undated (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-130)
  - Professional Development Program--Mike Priebe "The Ford Car Creative Product", 1994 (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-131)
  - Professional Development Program--Keith Woods "The Role of Research in Advertising", 1994 (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-132)
  - Randy Albright "RAG Creative Product", 1994 (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-133)
  - Randy Albright "RAG Creative Product", 1994 (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-134)
  - Red Cross focus group "donors", 1993 (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-135)
  - Relaunching Lux Luxo "4 stars", 1988 (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-136)
  - Research (Goodbye Guesswork) 27:00, Undated (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-137)
  - Research (Goodbye Guesswork) 27:00, Undated (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-138)
  - Rotella T Australia--Shell, Undated (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-139)
  - Sao Paulo--Brilhante detergent "Misterio Jornalista Legendado!" NTSC, Undated (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-140)
  - Sherwin Williams television commercials, 1997 (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-141)
  - Shooting Back: Photography by Homeless Children (Washington Project for the Arts documentary) 30:00, 1990 (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-142)
  - Smithsonian--Advertising 60:00, Undated (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-143)
  - Snake River Ranch video project part 1 (Stanley Resor family project), 2003 (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-144)
  - Successful Network Negotiating (Ron Fredrick), 1994 (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-145)
  - Summer of '42 (film), 1971 (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-146)
  - Television commercials (international compilation), Undated (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-147)
  - Tenneco/Monroe Sensa-Trac "Road" sequence, 1998 (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-148)
  - Thompson Total Branding Module--Direct Marketing 31:10, 1998 (Box V4, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-149)
  - Thompson Total Branding Module--Sales Promotion 28:25, 1998 (Box V5, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-150)
  - Thompson Total Branding Module--Sponsorship, 1998 (Box V5, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-151)
  - TTB Awards, Undated (Box V5, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-152)
  - U.S. Department of Justice--Drug Enforcement Administration A Profile, circa 1987 (Box V5, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-153)
  - U.S. Brewers historical reel, 2003 (Box V5, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-154)
  - United Way campaign film "On This Day", 1997 (Box V5, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-155)
  - Vietnam--Various creative, 2000 (Box V5, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-156)
  - WDIV Channel 4 6:00 News--JWT Move, 1998 (Box V5, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-157)
  - What Is a Brand? (Stephen King, Jeremy Bullmore), 1974 (Box V5, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-158)
  - White Castle "Do Your Part" :30, 1997 (Box V5, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-159)
  - White Castle retrospective, 1993 (Box V5, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-160)
  - Worth: Idea of Excellence, Undated (Box V5, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-161)
  - You Bet Your Life with Groucho Marx, 1987 (Box V5, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-162)
  - Video Strategies--82V00011 Section 1: Amusements, Leisure and Travel, 1981 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-163)
  - Video Strategies--82V00012 Appliances and Home Entertainment part 1, 1981 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-164)
  - Video Strategies--82V00013 Appliances and Home Entertainment part 2, 1981 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-165)
  - Video Strategies--82V00014 Automotive part 1, 1981 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-166)
  - Video Strategies--82V00015 Automotive part 2, 1981 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-167)
  - Video Strategies--82V00016 Beverages part 1, 1981 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-168)
  - Video Strategies--82V00017 Beverages part 2, 1981 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-169)
  - Video Strategies--82V00018 Cosmetics and Personal Hygiene part 1, 1981 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-170)
  - Video Strategies--82V00019 Cosmetics and Personal Hygiene part 2, 1981 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-171)
  - Video Strategies--82V00020 financial and Business Strategies, 1981 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-172)
  - Video Strategies--82V00021 Food part 1, 1981 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-173)
  - Video Strategies--82V00022 Food part 2, 1981 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-174)
  - Video Strategies--82V00023 Food Preparation, Snack Food, Pet Food part 1, 1981 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-175)
  - Video Strategies--82V00024 Food Preparation, Snack Food, Pet Food part 2, 1981 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-176)
  - Video Strategies--82V00025 Laundry and Paper Products part 1, 1981 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-177)
  - Video Strategies--82V00026 Laundry and Paper Products part 1, 1981 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-178)
  - Video Strategies--82V00027 Medicines, 1981 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-179)
  - Video Strategies--82V00028 Retail and Apparel part 1, 1981 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-180)
  - Video Strategies--82V00029 Retail and Apparel part 2, 1981 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-181)
  - Video Strategies--82V00030 Toys and Games, 1981 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-182)
  - Video Strategies--83V00027 Amusements, Leisure and Travel part 1, 1983 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-183)
  - Video Strategies--83V00028 Amusements, Leisure and Travel part 2, 1983 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-184)
  - Video Strategies--83V00029 Sections 2-3 (Appliances and home entertainment, Automotive), 1983 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-185)
  - Video Strategies--83V00030 Sections 4-5 (Beverages, Cosmetics and Personal Hygiene), 1983 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-186)
  - Video Strategies--83V00031 Financial and Business Services, 1983 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-187)
  - Video Strategies--83V00032 Sections 7 and 12 (Food, Toys and Games), 1983 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-188)
  - Video Strategies--83V00033 Sections 8-9 (Food Preparation, Snack Food, Pet Food; Laundry and Paper Products), 1983 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-189)
  - Video Strategies--83V00034 Sections; 10-11 (Medicines, Retail and Apparel), 1983 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-190)
  - Video Strategies--83V00036 Amusements, Leisure and Travel part 1, 1983 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-191)
  - Video Strategies--83V00037 Sections 2-3 (Appliances and home entertainment, Automotive), 1983 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-192)
  - Video Strategies--83V00038 Sections 4,5,8 (Beverages; Cosmetics and Personal Hygiene; Food Preparation, Snack Food, Pet Food), 1983 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-193)
  - Video Strategies--83V00039 Section 6,9 (Laundry and Paper Products; Financial and Business Services), 1983 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-194)
  - Video Strategies--83V00040 Sections 7,10 (Food; Medicines), 1983 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-195)
  - Video Strategies--83V00041 Sections 11,12 (Retail and Apparel; Toys and Games), 1983 (Box V6, Video-cassette RL00734-VHS-196)
  - Andrew Thompson showreel PAL 4:04, 2000 (Box B1, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-001)
  - Argentina--Elida Pond's Sedal Control PAL, 2000 (Box B1, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-002)
  - Argentina--Q2 reel, Undated (Box B1, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-003)
  - Australia--Ford, Herald Sun and Weekly Times, 2000 (Box B1, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-004)
  - Colombia--Portatil Heroes de Turno, 2000 (Box B1, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-005)
  - Drug Enforcement Administration--It Never Went Away: Voices of Heroin in the 90s" 11:56, 1999 (Box B1, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-006)
  - Golf Digest "Urinal", 2000 (Box B1, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-007)
  - Hong Kong--Asia Pacific 2nd quarter show reel (NTSC), 2000 (Box B1, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-008)
  - Korea--Commercials compilation, Undated (Box B1, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-009)
  - London--Compilation reel, Undated (Box B1, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-010)
  - London--EXCO NTSC 21:58, 2000 (Box B1, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-011)
  - London--Nestle NTSC 1:49, 2001 (Box B1, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-012)
  - London--Paris After Eight Dinner Party, 2000 (Box B1, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-013)
  - London--Reel for Chris Jones PAL, Undated (Box B1, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-014)
  - Paris--Rogale 10 spots, Undated (Box B1, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-015)
  - Paris--Rogale montage, 2000 (Box B1, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-016)
  - Portugal--BPI Bank Personal Credit NTSC, Undated (Box B2, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-017)
  - Portugal--Lithano Cheese; Governmental Road Accidents Prevention NTSC, Undated (Box B2, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-018)
  - Portugal--Onitelecom Internet, Undated (Box B2, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-019)
  - Portugal--Tape 1: BPI Bank Personal Credit PAL, Undated (Box B2, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-020)
  - Portugal--Tape 2: Onitelecom Internet PAL, Undated (Box B2, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-021)
  - Portugal--Tape 3: Lithano Cheese; Governmental Road Accidents Prevention PAL, Undated (Box B2, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-022)
  - PPGH/JWT (Amsterdam)--Harry Kramp Worldwide Creative Council, 2000 (Box B2, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-023)
  - Rio de Janeiro--2Q Creative, 2000 (Box B2, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-024)
  - Shanghai--Compilation reel, Undated (Box B2, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-025)
  - Shanghai--Compilation reel, Undated (Box B2, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-026)
  - Sydney--Compilation reel, Undated (Box B2, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-027)
  - Taipei--2nd Quarter compilation, Undated (Box B2, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-028)
  - Toronto--Funeral; Armistice Movie, 2000 (Box B2, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-029)
  - Toronto--Compilation, 2000 (Box B2, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-030)
  - Toronto--Kraft General Foods, 2000 (Box B2, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-031)
  - Venezuela--Agency reel, 2000 (Box B2, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-032)
  - Vietnam--April-June, 2000 (Box B3, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-033)
  - Worldwide Creative Council Global Tape 2 of 2, 2000 (Box B3, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-034)
  - Worldwide Creative Council Vietnam; Sydney; PPGH/Amsterdam, 2000 (Box B3, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-035)
  - Global Agency Network reel, 2000 (Box B3, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-036)
  - EXCO reel Cannes, 2000 (Box B3, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-037)
  - Worldwide reel Q2, 2000 (Box B3, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-038)
  - Worldwide reel 1st Quarter tape 2 of 2, Undated (Box B3, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-039)
  - Worldwide reel 1st Quarter tape 1 of 2, Undated (Box B3, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-040)
  - Worldwide Creative Council Global Tape 1 of 2, 2000 (Box B3, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-041)
  - Worldwide Creative Council Europe part 2 and Middle East, 2000 (Box B3, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-042)
  - Worldwide Creative Council Europe part 1, 2000 (Box B3, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-043)
  - Worldwide Creative Council Canada and Latin America, 2000 (Box B3, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-044)
  - Worldwide Creative Council Asia Pacific, 2000 (Box B3, Video-cassette RL00734-BETA-045)
  - Corbis Chicago--Kraft, 2007 (Box B3, Video-cassette RL00734-DBETA-001)
  - Kraft Home Town Hero promotion, 2007 (Box B3, Video-cassette RL00734-DBETA-002)
  - Kraft Philly Cream Cheese, 2006 (Box B3, Video-cassette RL00734-DBETA-003)
  - Professional Ladies, 1994 (Box A7, Video-cassette RL00734-8MM-001)
  - Troberman/Frost interviews; Kevin Maude 720P 59.94, 2008 (Box A7, Video-cassette RL00734-DVCAM-001)
  - Kraft Philly Cream Cheese film transfer master reel 2, 2006 (Box A7, Video-cassette RL00734-DVCAM-002)
  - Kraft Philly Cream Cheese film transfer master reel 1, 2006 (Box A7, Video-cassette RL00734-DVCAM-003)
  - JWT London, The Mill, "The Wave", 1999 (Box A13, Video-cassette RL00734-D1-001?)
  - JWT San Francisco: Creative Library (Sprint, Lyons), 1996 (Box F1, Video-reel RL00734-VID1-001)
  - JWT San Francisco: Creative Reel (Nestle, Sprint) 8 spots, 1996 (Box F1, Video-reel RL00734-VID1-002)
  - JWT San Francisco: Nestle Creative Reel, 1996 (Box F1, Video-reel RL00734-VID1-003)
- Computer Disk Files, 1991-2000; undated; 6
  - See DAT-006 through DAT-008; D8-003 (Box 2, Disk RL00734-FL3-001)
  - See DAT-005; D8-002 (Box 2, Disk RL00734-FL3-002)
  - See DAT-001 through DAT-002; D8-001 (Box 2, Disk RL00734-FL3-003)
  - See DAT-012 through DAT-013; D8-005 (Box 2, Disk RL00734-FL3-004)
  - See DAT-009 through DAT-011; D8-004 (Box 2, Disk RL00734-FL3-005)
  - See DAT-046 through DAT-048; D8-006 (Box 2, Disk RL00734-FL3-006)
  - Sydney--Smirnoff posters, 2000 (Box 2, Disk RL00734-FL3-007)
  - Melbourne--2nd Quarter Reviews, 2000 (Box 2, Disk RL00734-FL3-008)
  - Nabisco/Ritz Effie Awards Submission and print, 1999 (Box 2, Disk RL00734-FL3-009)
  - Tokyo--Creative Standard Review 2nd Quarter, best print, TTB, 2000 (Box 2, Disk RL00734-FL3-010)
  - Korea--Q2 Review: Allianz; Ford/Jaguar; Yuhan Kimberly, 2000 (Box 2, Disk RL00734-FL3-011)
  - Oral History Project (Transcript versions): De Angelo, Cronin (Box 2, Disk RL00734-FL3-012)
  - Oral History Project (Transcript versions): Connell, 1992 (Box 2, Disk RL00734-FL3-013)
  - Oral History Project (Transcript versions): Cronin; De Angelo; Dthompson; Sutton; Lanigan (ASCII/MAC) (Box 2, Disk RL00734-FL3-014)
  - Oral History Project (Transcript versions): Johnston (Box 2, Disk RL00734-FL3-015)
  - Oral History Project (Transcript versions): Lanigan (Box 2, Disk RL00734-FL3-016)
  - Oral History Project (Transcript versions): Lanigan final version, 1992 (Box 2, Disk RL00734-FL3-017)
  - Oral History Project (Transcript versions): Senior (Box 2, Disk RL00734-FL3-018)
  - Oral History Project (Transcript versions): D Thompson (Box 2, Disk RL00734-FL3-019)
  - Oral History Project (Transcript versions): Webster interview (Box 2, Disk RL00734-FL3-020)
  - Oral History Project (Transcript versions): Wilson, Edward B. interview, 1991 (Box 2, Disk RL00734-FL3-021)